【鬼畜万恶之源： 美国肯德基 2019年母亲节广告】
【来源： KFC Chickendales】
字幕制作： Sam Toki
完工日期： 2020年 5月 11日（周一）
本字幕无版权限制
哦 老妈 最近过得怎样？
Oh, how are you, mom?
我听说你是世界上最好的母亲
I hear you are the best mom in the world.
如何？
Well?
你们觉得呢？ 臭小子们
What do you think♂, boys?
叮！
Ding!
唔！
Woo!
我爱你 老妈
I love you, mom.
呼！
Hoo!
你是一位独一无二的淑女
You are a really special lady.
做——
HOW...
做这个——
HOW DOES...
做这个世界——
HOW DOES IT...
做这个世界上——
HOW DOES IT FEEL...
做这个世界上最——
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE...
做这个世界上最酷——
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE THE...
做这个世界上最酷的——
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE THE COOLEST...
做这个世界上最酷的老妈——
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE THE COOLEST MOM...
做这个世界上最酷的老妈感觉——
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE THE COOLEST MOM IN...
做这个世界上最酷的老妈感觉不错吧！
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE THE COOLEST MOM IN THE WORLD
母亲节快乐！
Happy Mother's Day!
呼！
Fuu!